illimitux.net 2010-12-30

# Illimitux | Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website. As you can see, Illimitux is accessible via www.illimitux.net or illimitux.com, for technical reasons. These domain names redirect to the same site.   
This Privacy Policy explains how our extension and FireFox ® collects information. When you click or check the boxes "Continue", "Download", or any other similar button during your initial registration on our website, we are informed about your membership agreement below. 

##  Site navigation 

When you visit our website, our Web server automatically records the name of your Internet service provider, the website from which you contact us, the pages of our sites you browse and the date and duration of your visit .   
Our site uses cookies for several purposes. These cookies could be used to track your online activities. As with most websites, some of our partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). If you are concerned about this, we recommend you disable third-party cookies in your browser preferences (Please note that we have no access or control over these cookies). Our ads come from Google Adsense. Please check the respective web site's privacy policies.   
On the other hand, we use Google Analytics to collect anonymous information about your navigation on our site. We analyze this information to examine trends, administer the site, monitor the movement of users in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We use this information to improve navigation and analyze the flow on our site. 

## Using the extension _Illimitux_

When you install this extension, the application collects only the video ID (ID), the platform used, and the date/version used. This is used to complete the purpose of the application: To remove restrictions on streaming platforms. 

##  Personal Information 

If you contact us for technical support, partnership request, or for any other reason, we will communicate by e-mail. Your email address will not be disclosed, given, or sold to anyone, including third parties. In the case of an exchange of mail for technical support, we can publish the contents of the e-mail (without personal information like email or IP address) to our Frequently Asked Questions. This could be an effective source for other users. 

## Amendments to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to make changes to our Privacy Policy, they will be posted on this site to keep you updated about the latest version. To keep updated about changes, please regularly review the contents of this page.   
In accordance with this Privacy Policy, we may use or disclose identifiable information other than those described herein without informing you or giving you the opportunity to consent to such amendments on the use and disclosure of your data.
